为了使得 preference 显示在手机上，我们
To make the preferences appear on the phone, we
需要修改SettingsActivity。在Oncreate方法中
need to modify settings activity. In the on-create method
我们将重写一些代码
we're going to replace this to do with some code.
我们将用addPreferencesFromResource调用我们定义的pref_general.xml文件
We're going to call addPreferencesFromResource with the pref_general xml
我们需要将
that we defined. Then we need to bind the
location preference的值赋给preference summary
preference summary to the value of the location preference.
这意味着当用户修改preference时
This means that when the user changes the preference,
标签下面的值将会更新
the summary value underneath the label will be updated.
如果你看一下这个方法的声明
If you look at the declaration of this method,
可以看到对于一个给定的preference
we see that for a given preference, it sets a
它在preference中设置了一个监听事件，如果你
preference change listener on it. If you scroll to
滑动到顶部，你会看到SettingsActivity实际上已经实现了
the top, you see that the settings activity actually implements
OnPreferenceChangelistener的接口。这个方法
the interface on preference change listener. That method is
在下面我们重载OnPreferenceChange方法的地方可以找到
found down below, where we override the onPreferenceChange
记住我们的location Preference实际上是一个
method. Remember that our location preference is actually an
edit text preference。所以它并不会陷入这种情况中
edit text preference. So, it won't fall into this case,
但是它会陷入下面的这种情况当中
but it will fall in this case down here. Then,
然后在设置的UI界面中你可以看到摘要
in the settings UI you can see that the summary
现在是这个值。在你的应用中尝试做这些改变吧
is now this value. Make these changes in your app.
看看这节课老师为你所需要的代码行所做的笔记
See the instructor notes for the lines of code you need.